原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我叫卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Kara Zor-El.
我来自氪星
I'm from Krypton.
我来到这颗星球避难
I'm a refugee on this planet.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我被派往地球保护我的堂弟
I was sent to Earth to protect my cousin.
但我的太空舱被击中后偏离路线
But my pod got knocked off course.
在我到达地球之时
And by the time I got here,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的堂弟已经长大  成为了超人
my cousin had already grown up and become... Superman.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我隐藏了我的真实身份
I hid who I really was
直到最近的一起事故
until one day when an accident
迫使我向世界揭示了自己的身份
forced me to reveal myself to the world.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
对于大多数人  我只是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
To most people, I'm a reporter at CatCo Worldwide Media.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
但私下里  我与收养家庭的姐姐一同为超查部工作
But in secret I work with my adopted sister at the DEO
保护这颗我称之为家园的星球
to protect this planet I call my home
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不受任何人的伤害
from anyone that means to cause it harm.
我是超女
I am Supergirl.
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
我和地方检察官谈过话了  詹姆斯
I talked to the DA, James.
我拿信息跟她交换  她就撤销了指控
I traded information, she dropped the indictment.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
如果那些人是
People feeling inferior
因为害怕低人一等才加入仇恨组织
is what makes them join these hate groups,
那我们就让他们公平竞争
then we could level the playing field.
-是哈伦·艾尔造成的吗  -哈伦让心脏坚不可摧
- Did the Harun-El do this? - It made the heart invincible.
我的家人  他们来自纳尔托尔星球
My family, they're from a planet called Naltor.
每一代
Once in a generation,
我们种族的一些女性会遗传梦见未来的能力
some of our women, they can dream the future.
我们要知道你的秘密身份
We need to know your secret identity.
很抱歉  阁下  恕难从命
I'm sorry, sir. I can't give you what you want.
那我就只有感谢你的付出了
Then, I thank you for your service,
你被解雇了  立即生效
but you're dismissed, effective immediately.
她可以被控制住了吗
我们的朋友正在努力
很好
但她的对手可不只是坦克
加紧训练她
三  二  一
And three, two, one...
休息
Recover.
真是不错的运动
It's a great workout, huh?
是啊
Ooh! Yeah.
真棒  我都能感受到脂肪在燃烧
So good. I can feel the burn.
我需要这个
I needed this.
我们好久没有一起出来过了
It's been too long since we've hung out.
-是啊  你太忙了  -我知道
- Yeah, I know, you've been so busy. - Yeah, I know, I...
我埋头于这些我独立运作的项目
I get so deep into these projects where I'm working alone,
周围没有可以与我讨论或支持我的人
without any sounding board or support.
是  独自工作是比较艰难  但也很令人振奋
Yeah, working alone can be tough, but exciting, too.
我堂弟独自工作了好几年
My cousin's worked alone for years,
之前他跟我讲过感受
and he was telling me about it the other day.
其实挺鼓舞人心的
It was inspiring, actually.
而且你可以和詹姆斯无所不谈
And you have James to talk about everything with.
一定很不错
I'm sure that's nice.
也不是无所不谈
Well, not everything.
你知道詹姆斯什么样
Well, you know how James can be.
你们感恩节之后还没和好吗
You guys haven't made up since Thanksgiving?
你应该和他谈谈
You should talk to him.
他或许比你想象中更开明
He might be more open-minded than you expect.
如果他不是呢
And if he's not?
我就帮你揍他
I'll beat him up for you.
求救求救  我是麦卡利斯特  请求援助
Mayday. Mayday. This is McAllister. Backup needed!
卡拉  你还好吗
Kara, you okay?
抽筋了  太糟糕了
Ugh, cramps. Really bad.
我去...  我去冰敷一下
I'm gonna... I'm going to go ice it.
好吧
Okay.
不好
Oh, no.
先生
Sir?
麦卡利斯特上校
Colonel McAllister?
超 女
第四季 第九集
她有脑震荡  还有两根肋骨断了
She has a concussion and two broken ribs,
但是没有内出血
but no internal bleeding.
我很惊讶会在这里看到你  超女
I'm surprised to see you here, Supergirl.
我以为总统将你从超查部解雇时
I thought the President was pretty clear
已经说得很清楚了
when he dismissed you from the DEO.
上校  我来这里不是因为超查部
Colonel, I didn't come here because of the DEO.
我来这里是因为人们需要帮助
I came here because there were people who needed help.
如果超女是第一个到达犯罪现场的
If Supergirl was the first one on the crime scene,
或许她能帮助我们找出是谁干的
then maybe she can help us figure out who did it.
那边还有一具尸体  麦卡利斯特上校
There was another body right there, a Colonel McAllister,
但是他被一个外星人拉下船了
but he was dragged overboard by an alien.
什么样的外星人
What kind of alien?
全身都是微弱的折射反光
It was a shimmer of refracted light.
所以你能提供的就是一片微光
So, all you have to contribute is a shimmer?
说实话  上校
To be fair, Colonel,
若不是超女  我们连这条信息也未必知道
that's more information than we would have had otherwise.
我可以帮忙收集证据
I'm sure I could help with evidence,
我就是还没有时间四处调查
I just... I haven't had a chance to look around.
谢谢你  但这里是超查部的犯罪现场了
Thank you, but this is a DEO crime scene now.
你已经造成了严重的污染
You've contaminated it enough already.
如果不是我
If it weren't for me,
这里就根本成不了犯罪现场
there wouldn't be a crime scene to begin with.
如果我没来这里
If I hadn't come here,
这船就会被炸弹炸成碎片
a bomb would've blown this ship to smithereens,
所有海豹突击队员都会死
and all the SEALs would've died.
我没时间和你争吵
I don't have time to argue with you.
我还得去找你放跑的那个杀人外星人
I have to locate the murderous alien you let escape.
让开吧
So, move aside.
这是命令
That is an order.
我不会因为不在超查部工作了
Just because I don't work at the DEO anymore,
就放弃继续做英雄
doesn't mean I'm going to stop being a hero.
不管你说什么
No matter what you say.
私家侦探
抱歉  我们还没开张...
Oh, hi, sorry. We're not quite open yet--
布莱尼
Brainy.
你好  荣恩
Hello, J'onn.
不错
Yes.
所以这是你的新事业了
So, this is your new business.
有人说开私人侦探社挺老套的
Some would say launching a PI shingle is a bit old-fashioned.
但话又说回来  你本来就够老的
But, then again, you are very old.
布莱尼  过去这几个月里
You know, Brainy, in the last couple of months,
我帮助了很多人
I've had the chance to help people,
那些不能去报警的人类与外星人
humans and aliens who can't go to the police.
自从离开超查部  我就试图另辟蹊径
I've been trying to carve out a path ever since I left the DEO,
现在感觉走对路了
and, yeah, this feels about right.
说到离开超查部
Speaking of leaving the DEO,
我是为了超女而来
I'm here to talk about Supergirl.
她会需要支援  资源  得力助手
She's going to require backup, resources, a girl Friday...
我相信你这个得力助手正适合她
And I believe you are just the girl Friday for the job.
我可以预付现金
I could pay you cash in advance.
-我不能收你的钱  -为什么不能
- I can't take your money for that. - Why not?
你想要更多吗  我有更多
Do you want more? I have more.
不  布莱尼  我不能收你的钱
No, Brainy, I can't take your money for that.
拜托  收起来  快收起来
Please. Put it away, put it away.
假如超女需要我  她开口就好
Look, if Supergirl needs me, all she has to do is ask.
不过  既然你提到了这点
But, since you mentioned it,
我会让她知道我有空帮忙
I'll let her know that I'm available.
谢谢你  荣恩
Thank you, J'onn.
不用谢
No problem.
布莱尼  你掉东西了
Uh, Brainy, you, uh, dropped something.
-不  原本就在那  -不  是你掉的
- No, that was there-- - No, you dropped it.
那你把账单寄给我吧
You'll send me the bill, then.
我原本希望超女被解雇后
I had hoped that after she was fired,
能少去见义勇为  比如阻止失控列车
Supergirl might limit her heroics to stopping runaway trains
上树救猫咪等等
and saving kittens from trees.
我太天真了
That was naive.
世上最强大的外星人逍遥在外
The most powerful alien in the world is out there,
而她显然想给我们
and she clearly has every intention
添更多麻烦
on making our lives more difficult.
新消息  卡拉
海岸警卫队没有该船记录  有什么线索吗
忽略  回复
总统不该在没有应急计划的情况下
The President should never have dismissed her
那样解雇她
without a contingency plan.
我也从没听过什么微光外星人  你呢
And I've never heard of a shimmering alien, have you?
没有  但话说回来
No. But, then again,
我也记不全所有记录在案的外星人生命形式
I'm not familiar with every cataloged alien life form.
你的首要任务是确认这起袭击背后的生物
Priority one for you is to ID and neutralize the creature
并将其制伏
who was behind the attack.
与此同时  我要去审问沃尔夫特工
Meanwhile, I'm going to interrogate Agent Wolf.
你为什么要审问沃尔夫特工
Why are you interrogating Agent Wolf?
我要纠正总统的错误
I'm going to correct the President's mistake
确保超女从今往后听从我们的命令
and make sure Supergirl listens to us from now on.
你要怎样做到这点
How are you going to do that?
超女虽然麻烦  但她不是天才
Supergirl is an annoyance, but she's no genius.
她在超查部的那段时间里
At some point during her time here,
肯定有人在某个时刻看到了什么
someone must have seen something
能成为查出她秘密身份的线索
that's a clue to her secret identity.
我只需要找到一个线头
And all I need is one loose strand,
就能揭开这层神秘的面纱
and I'll unravel this mystery.
我长话短说
I'll make this quick.
只有你们几位特工知道超女的秘密身份
You are the only agents that know Supergirl's secret identity,
哈雷上校目前的唯一目标
and Colonel Haley has only one focus right now,
就是把它查出来
that's to uncover it.
一旦她查到超女的身份
Once she has Supergirl's identity,
她相信她可以重新让超女听命于她
she believes she can reassert control and keep Supergirl in line.
保守这个秘密
Keeping that information safe
意味着当哈雷与你们对质时
means that if Haley confronts you,
你们将对上级长官说谎
you will be lying to a superior officer.
我们谁都不想危害到超女或你
None of us wants to compromise Supergirl or you,
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers.
我不能要求你们做有违道德准则的事
I can't ask you to do anything against your moral code.
但我要你们深刻考虑一下
But I am asking that you deeply consider
我们目前共同的处境
the situation we are in together.
我会尽力保护超女
I'll do whatever I can to protect Supergirl.
我也一样
Same for me.
假如遭到对质  我们可以利用抗审训练
If confronted, we could use our RTI training.
假如没有
If not,
我们发誓保持沉默
we vow to remain silent.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers.
哈雷上校
Colonel Haley.
你和这些特工在商讨什么具体情况吗
Are you and these agents working on something specific?
就早上的袭击事件做说明
Uh, debrief on the morning's attack.
在这种地方说明  挺有趣的
Interesting place for a debriefing.
劳伦斯特工  我要和你谈谈
Agent Lawrence, I need to speak with you.
其余人解散
Everyone else, dismissed.
差点被抓到
Well, that was a close call.
-抗审训练是什么  -抵抗审讯
- What is RTI training? - Resistance to Interrogation.
我不需要那个
I don't need that.
我最近将我的神经网络
I've recently restructured my neural network
重组成多个小区域
to form many small compartments
用以存储敏感信息
for storing sensitive information.
我为什么一点都不惊讶呢
Why does that not surprise me?
如有需要
If I so desire it,
我可以在指定时间内
I can shut down all access to one or more compartments
禁止访问一个或多个区域
for a designated amount of time.
真遗憾你们都没有这种能力
I'm sorry none of you share the same capacity.
当然  我在竭尽全力确保超女安全
Of course I'm doing everything I can to keep Supergirl safe.
我知道  布莱尼
I know you are, Brainy.
我感觉她在外面需要更多支援
I have a sense she needs more support out there.
无论哈雷怎样  我和卡拉都仍是搭档
Kara and I, we're still partners, despite Haley.
事实上  她刚发来信息
In fact, she just texted that
说海岸警卫队没有那艘货船的记录
the Coast Guard has no record of that cargo ship.
这意味着被她救下的海豹突击队员醒来后
Which means that we're going to have to talk to that Navy SEAL
我们必须第一时间找她谈话
that she saved as soon as she wakes up.
是啊  关于这点
Yes, about that.
那名被超查部监护的海豹突击队员
The Navy SEAL was taken out of DEO custody and has...
我该怎么说呢
Well, how shall I put this?
-消失了  -"消失了"是什么意思
- Disappeared. - What do you mean, "Disappeared"?
她被转移到哪  或由谁监护
There's no record of where she was transferred
全然没有记录
or whose custody she's in.
奇怪
That's odd.
那好  我们先调查麦卡利斯特上校
Okay, well, then let's start looking into McAllister,
-查出他...  -我无法
- find out what he -- - I was unable to
在政府数据库中定位麦卡利斯特上校
locate Colonel McAllister in the government database,
也没有他的秘密行动记录
none in black ops either.
好吧  货船不存在
Okay, so there's no cargo ship,
我们唯一的目击者消失了
our only witness has disappeared,
麦卡利斯特也没有记录
and there's no record of McAllister,
而我们确定他在那艘船上遇害
who we know was killed on that ship.
-听起来像掩盖证据  -是啊
- Sounds like a cover-up. - Yeah.
沒有任何记录
There is no records of anything.
也许他们也利用那个炸弹
So maybe they were trying to use that bomb
来销毁所有的物理证据
to, you know, destroy all the physical evidence, too.
人们为什么要隐瞒事实
Why do people cover things up?
他们应该知道我们迟早会发现的
They should just know that we're going to figure it out.
说到这个
Yeah, well, speaking of which...
我很不想提这件事
I hate to bring this up because
因为我不想让你更生气
I don't want to upset you any more,
但是哈雷要调查超女的身份
but Haley, she's on a mission to find out who Supergirl is.
把我给解雇了还不够吗
It's not enough that I got fired?
她想知道你的真实身份
Well, she wants to know your identity,
好用来控制你
so that she can use it to keep you in line.
所以请你低调一点
So, please, stay off of her radar.
好
Okay.
反正跟踪线索已经没有了
So anyway, the clue trail has gone cold.
也不一定
Not necessarily.
只有你见过那个外星人的长相
I mean, you were the only one that saw what the alien looks like.
那道微光
Right, the shimmer.
但超查部没人听说过这类外星人吧
But no one at the DEO has heard of an alien like that, right?
也许我们是时候去找那个
Maybe it's time we talked to somebody
比我们俩都先进超查部的人了
who was at the DEO before either of us were.
敲敲门
Knock, knock.
莉娜
Hey, Lena.
我知道你一直想和我谈谈
I know you've been wanting to connect,
但我一直在忙自己的事情  腾不出空来
but I've been stuck inside myself and I haven't been available.
没事  我明白  你一直在忙工作
No, it's okay. I get it. You're always working.
是的
I am.
但我也没陪在你身边  现在我想做些改变
But I've also been absent, and I'm here to change that.
告诉我你在想什么
So, just tell me what's on your mind.
当你和我说
When you told me that you...
你要帮我解决起诉的事
How you helped me with the indictment,
道德骄傲冲昏了我的头脑
I jumped on my moral high horse
让我趾高气扬
and I rode it into the sunset,
而我觉得生气是合乎情理的
and I felt pretty justified about being angry.
但是在我经过了自由之子的事情后
But after everything I went through with the Children of Liberty,
我不得不重新考虑一些事情
I had to rethink some things.
我看了你的文章
I read your article.
我明白你经历了什么
I understand what you went through.
有些事我没写出来
I left some things out.
比如我如何谴责我心爱的女人
Like how I condemned the woman I love
出卖了我  或者我认为她出卖了我
for selling out, or what I perceived to be selling out,
但当我被迫身处同样的位置时
but when I was forced into the same position,
我也做了同样的抉择
I did the same thing.
没人会怪你的  尤其是我
No one will blame you for that, least of all me.
不是责怪的问题  只是
It's not blame, it's just...
当自由代表想要我犯法的时候
When Agent Liberty wanted me to break the law,
当他想要我炸毁纪念碑的时候
when he wanted me to blow up the monument,
我是出于自愿的
I was willing to.
因为你当时想要救人
Because you wanted to save someone.
就和你救我一样
Just like you saved me.
我明白
I get it.
有时候只要目的正当  确实可以不择手段
Sometimes the ends do justify the means.
我想告诉你一件事
I want you to know something.
我明白做出艰难抉择的意义
I understand what it means to make hard choices,
但是我一直做错了
and I've been wrong.
你不知道你这番话对我有多重要
You don't know how much it means to me to hear you say that.
我不知道  有多重要呢
No, I don't. How much does it mean?
-这么重要  -好
- About this much. - Oh, okay.
-我是尼娅·纳尔  -尼娅·纳尔
- Nia Nal. - Nia Nal.
-布莱尼  -正是在下
- Brainy? - None other.
没想到你会打来  你好吗
This is a nice surprise. How are you?
我打来是想问问你喜不喜欢吃东西
I am calling to find out about food, and your interest in it.
我当然喜欢吃东西
Uh, I'm definitely interested in food.
凯特科全球媒体公司
你想要吃点东西吗
Would you like to eat some?
现在吗  在电话里吃吗
Now? Like, on the phone with you?
什么  不是  一起出去吃
What? No. In person.
我在想去一个公众场所
And I am thinking at a public place
有人给同样喜欢食物的人提供服务的地方
where food is served to other people who also appreciate it.
你是说餐厅吗
You mean, a restaurant.
布莱尼  你在约我吗
Brainy, are you asking me out?
是的
Yes.
-我答应你  -棒  一会见
- The answer is yes. - Excellent. See you soon.
喂
Hello?
我们还没计划好  你就挂电话了
You hung up before we could make a plan.
难道你不觉得我们应该选个时间和地点吗
Don't you think we should pick a time and place?
-是的  -多克斯特工
- Yes, of course. - Agent Dox.
几分钟我会回电告诉你的  尼娅·纳尔
I shall return to this thought in a few minutes, Nia Nal.
等一下
Wait, wha--
布莱尼
Brainy?
是  哈雷上校
Yes, Colonel Haley?
我要和你谈谈超女的事  跟我来
I need to speak to you about Supergirl. Follow me.
荣恩  这里很不错啊
J'onn, this is great.
谢谢你  卡拉
Oh, thank you, Kara.
我很喜欢这个地方
I got a really good feeling about this place.
瞧  只要看到这个  就知道你已经搬进来了
Look, this is the only thing you need to know you've moved in.
微光外星人和一艘不存在的货船
So, shimmering aliens and a non-existent cargo ship.
听起来像是间谍小说里的情节
Sounds like the plot of a spy novel.
嗯  有让你想起些什么吗
Yeah. Did it ring any bells?
没有  但是幸好
No. But, lucky for you,
我保留了我在超查部整个任职期间的文件
I did keep files from my entire tenure at the DEO.
看来我有先见之明
I guess I had the foresight
知道这些迟早会派上用场
to know that this might come in handy.
你保留了好多记录
You kept so many records.
这是艾丽克斯的背景调查
This is Alex's background check
从她第一天在超查部工作开始
from when she first started at the DEO.
看看这些违规停车罚单
Look at all those parking tickets.
她照顾了我这么久
She's looked out for me for so long.
我以为我离开超查部会让她松口气
I thought my leaving the DEO would give her a break,
但是她还在保护我不受哈雷的侵害
but she's still protecting me against Haley.
保护你是她的天职
Protecting you is in her DNA.
这里有一份来历不明外星人的移交单
Here's a transfer form for aliens of unknown origin.
莫拉外星人
Aliens called Morae.
莫拉  我从来没听说过他们
Morae? I've never heard of them before.
莫拉人天生具有隐身能力
"Morae have a natural cloaking ability
用于对抗突袭
useful for surprise attacks."
上面写着他们有隐身能力
Oh, it says they're invisible,
但我看到了一片微光
but I saw a shimmer.
也许他们对所有人是隐形的  除了你之外
Maybe they're invisible to everybody else except you
因为你的X光视线
because of your X-ray vision.
是谁进行的征调
Who did the requisition?
一位叫阿方索·谭的监管
A General Alfonso Tan.
我好像之前见过这个名字...
I think I saw that name earlier...
在哪呢...
Where did I...
这里
Here it is.
"阿方索·谭将军  莫拉计划的首席指挥官"
"General Alfonso Tan, Chief Commanding Officer of Project Morae,
于2012年将控制权交给...
handed over control in 2012 to...
兰德尔·麦卡利斯特上校
A Colonel Randall McAllister."
就是船上死掉的家伙  看来确实有这个人啊
That's the guy who died on the boat. So he does exist.
证明有人想隐瞒事实
This is proof that there was a cover-up.
问题是  为什么要隐瞒呢
The question is, why are they covering it up?
不知道  这是绝密计划  大部分都被编改过
I don't know. It was a top-secret program, most of it's redacted.
我们应该找谭将军谈谈  他或许能解释
We should talk to General Tan. He might be able to explain.
等等
Wait a second.
负责这个计划的不止谭将军和麦卡利斯特
General Tan and McAllister weren't the only ones on this project.
还有一个名字...
There's another name...
劳伦·哈雷上校
Colonel Lauren Haley.
布莱尼  你没事吧
Brainy, hey, are you okay?
我有一次在维内加星球上
I was once interrogated for 18 straight days
被伊科弗瑞伊尔科那个绿色的吸血怪
on the planet Venegar by Ik'Lofrai'iork,
一连盘问了18天
the emerald bloodeater.
而我告诉你  哈雷上校
And let me tell you, Colonel Haley
跟那个十只眼的野兽有的一拼
would give that ten-eyed beast a run for his money.
但你什么也没告诉她吧
But you didn't tell her anything, right?
没什么可说的
Eh, there was nothing to tell.
她只是一直问我超女的身份
She just kept asking me about Supergirl's identity.
所以你用大脑分区功能储存了卡拉的信息
So, you used your brain compartmentalizing thing with Kara.
这跟卡拉有什么关系
What does Kara have to do with anything?
这是永久性的吗
Is this permanent
还是说你很快又会想起她是超女了
or are you going to remember that she's Supergirl soon?
卡拉
Kara?
你那戴眼镜的妹妹
Your sister with the glasses?
幽默啊  部长
Good one, Director.
她俩看起来一点都...
They don't even look anything... Oh.
对  我的分区功能是有时间限制的
Yes, my compartmentalization was on a timer.
好吧
Okay.
卡拉  怎么了
Kara. Hey. What's up?
好  我得走了  你要不坐下休息会吧
Okay. I have to go. Hey, just maybe sit down.
哈雷看见你离开了吗
Did Haley see you leave?
没有  她忙着审问特工呢
No, she's too busy interrogating agents.
她总是这么自以为是
She's always so self-righteous,
但如果我们查出来她和这事有关
but if we find out that she's been involved in this,
我和她一块工作的日子就不长了
I might not have to work with her for very much longer.
希望能从谭那里得到答案吧
Let's just hope Tan has some answers.
跟着我
Follow my lead.
谭  你在干什么
Tan. What are you doing?
亨肖  超女  你们必须离开
Henshaw? Supergirl? You need to leave.
我是超查部部长丹弗斯
I'm Director Danvers of the DEO.
我们有问题要问你
We have some questions for you.
我不回答任何问题
I'm not answering any questions.
莫拉计划是什么
What is Project Morae,
你和哈雷为什么要隐瞒麦卡利斯特的死亡
and why are you and Haley covering up McAllister's death?
这是机密  亨肖
It's top secret, Henshaw.
那意味着  不关你们的事  走开
That means none of your business. Out of my way.
你不把知道的说出来  哪都不许去
You're not going anywhere until you tell us what you know.
如果你想离开这里
If you want to get out of here,
就告诉我们真相
then you're going to have to tell us the truth.
行  我们在莫拉人小的时候发现了他们
Fine, we found the Morae as children.
他们的隐身技能超出我们所见过的任何技术
Their cloaking ability is beyond any technology we've ever seen,
所以我们就带走了他们  训练他们
so we took them and we trained them.
训练他们干什么
Trained them for what?
保护我们的国家  他们是国家的安全资产
To protect our nation, they're security assets.
你是说杀手吧
You mean assassins?
你把外星人小孩训练成杀手
You trained alien children to be killers?
他们很出色
And they were amazing.
比我见过的任何队伍都强  成功率百分之百
Like no unit I've ever seen, 100% success rate.
而现在他们要来报复我了
And now they're coming for me.
-他们为什么变坏了  -因为我们想杀了他们
- Why did they go bad? - Because we tried to kill 'em.
总统下令要断绝
The President sent down the order
与所有外星人员的联系
to cut ties with all alien personnel,
我就命令麦卡利斯特除掉他们
so I gave McAllister the order to neutralize them.
货船本是一次伏击
The cargo ship was an ambush.
对  但莫拉人预料到了
Yes, but the Morae saw it coming.
于是他们就反攻  灭掉海豹突击队后逃跑了
So they fought back, killed the SEAL team, and escaped.
但他们是军人  是你的同盟
But they were soldiers. They were your allies.
他们不是人类  他们是杀人机器
They're not human. They're killing machines.
他们无法被控制
And they can't be contained.
-你看见什么了吗  -有两个莫拉人
- Do you see anything? - There's two of them.
别走
Stay here.
谭  我们可以保护你  别跑
Tan, we can protect you. Don't run.
艾丽克斯  待在我身边
Alex, stay next to me.
-你看见什么了吗  -等一下
- Do you see anything? - Just give me a sec.
好吧  我什么都没看到  你看得见吗
Okay, I don't see anything, can you?
看不见  一点微光都没有
No. No, not even a glimmer.
谭  停车
Tan, stop the car.
谭
Tan?
我们不是来伤害你的
We're not here to hurt you.
我是外星人
I'm an alien.
我为政府工作  他们也要对付我
I worked for the government, and they turned on me, too.
但杀掉伤害你的人并没有用
But killing the people that hurt you won't do any good.
我们带它回超查部
Let's get it back to the DEO.
不不不  我们不想伤害你
No, no, no. We don't want to hurt you.
不去超查部
No DEO.
不见哈雷
No Haley.
不
No.
-谭将军死了  -什么
- General Tan is dead. - What?
谭死了  要不是你骗我
Tan is dead, and if you hadn't lied to me,
我们原本能救他的
we could have saved his life.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
莫拉计划
Project Morae.
莫拉人杀了麦卡利斯特  又杀了谭
The Morae killed McAllister, and then they killed Tan.
你为什么要隐瞒
Why are you covering this up?
我什么都没有隐瞒  丹弗斯
I'm not covering anything up, Danvers.
我很多年前就和莫拉人没有关系了
I haven't had anything to do with the Morae for years.
你觉得我会信吗
You expect me to believe that?
你觉得我会故意妨碍调查吗
You think I would knowingly impede an investigation?
我从未和麦卡利斯特上校工作过
I've never worked with any Colonel McAllister,
当超女把那些外星人形容为微光的时候
and when Supergirl described the aliens as shimmers,
我信了她的话
I took her at her word.
因为她的X光视线  超女看见了微光
Because of her X-ray vision, Supergirl sees shimmers,
而其余的人什么都看不见
while the rest of us see nothing.
-所以莫拉人失控了  -没错
- So, the Morae are loose? - Yes.
谭下令摧毁他们  但是他们反击了
Tan gave an order to neutralize them, but they fought back,
然后逃跑了
and they escaped.
我们就快抓到一只
Now we almost captured one,
但是我们一说要被你关着
but then it killed itself at the mention
他就自杀了
of being brought back into your custody.
你对它做了什么
What did you do to it?
对于年纪达标的外星人的标准做法
Standard protocol with tender-age aliens.
用创伤使它们遵守纪律和服从我们
Trauma as a method of discipline and obedience.
我们知道如果它们惧怕我们
We knew that if they feared us,
它们就会服从我们  事实也是如此
they would obey us, and they did.
什么样的创伤
What kind of trauma?
你不该为这件事感到愤怒  丹弗斯
Your sense of outrage is misplaced, Danvers.
它们不是人类
They aren't humans.
但它们是有情众生  不是吗
But they are sentient beings, aren't they?
它们为了复仇杀了麦卡利斯特和谭
When they killed McAllister and Tan for vengeance.
你所做的一切  你都觉得是正确的吗
I mean, none of what you've done, it strikes you as wrong?
你以为我们要如何保卫国家的安危
How do you think we keep this country safe?
战争中的每个士兵
Every soldier in every war
都会做一些他们觉得糟糕的事情
has had to do things they considered awful.
这就是现实
Now this is reality.
有时候现实是残酷的
Sometimes reality is messy,
是丑陋和令人不适的
and it's ugly and uncomfortable.
你最终就会做一些你认为永远不会做的事
And you end up doing things you thought you'd never do.
如果你说的是真的
If what you're telling me is true,
剩下的两个莫拉人接下来会找我复仇
the two Morae that are left are going to come for me next.
让超查部做好迎接袭击的准备
Prepare the DEO for an assault.
让我直奔这次会议的主题
Now, let me get right to the purpose of this meeting.
会议
A meeting?
我以为这是个约会
I thought we were on a date.
约会  这不是个约会
A date? This isn't a date.
如果是个约会  我们就会做些有趣的事
If it were a date, we'd be doing something fun,
比如彩弹射击或者密室
like paintball or an escape room.
我现在感觉自己像个傻子
Well, now I feel like an idiot.
我只是有些困惑
I'm just confused.
我从没想过像你一样漂亮的人
I never thought anyone as beautiful as you
会对我这样的人感兴趣
would be interested in someone like me.
我不确定我是不是对你感兴趣
Well, I'm not sure that I am interested in you.
显然  我把事情搞砸了
Clearly, I've made a mess of things.
我本意不是如此
Not my intention.
但是我今天来和你说的事
But the thing I came to talk to you about
很重要
today is important.
我能继续了吗
Should I proceed?
好的  好的  我很好奇
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, I'm curious...
是超女
It's Supergirl.
既然你现在开始用梦境的能力了
Since you're now using your dreaming abilities,
我认为你可能会想和超女一起
I thought that you may be interested in joining her
打击罪犯
on her many crime-fighting
以及拯救星球
and/or planet-saving adventures
作为一个朋友
as sort of a friend.
有超能力的朋友
A Super friend.
布莱尼  在科林伍德发生的事
Brainy, what happened in Collinwood was...
我觉得那不过是偶发的事情
I think that was more of a one-time thing.
但是你很擅长处理
But you were so good at it.
我都没准备好讨论这件事
I'm not even really prepared to discuss this.
我本在一条黑暗的路上
I was on a dark path.
我被逮捕了
I was arrested,
但是被给予了改变的机会
and I was given a choice to change
并将我的智力为善服务
and to use my intellect in the service of good.
一开始  我不想承担这样的责任
At first, I didn't want the responsibilities
承担超级英雄的重任
or burdens of a superhero.
但我的确选择了这条路
But I did choose.
并从没后悔过
And I haven't regretted it.
你是一个英雄  我知道的
You are a hero, I know it.
我要走了
I need to go.
这个文件夹里包含了一些战衣的想法
This binder contains some costume ideas
以及一些可能的代号
and some code name possibilities.
请认真想一想我说过的话
Please think about what I've said.
我真不敢相信你在做小蛋糕
I can't believe you're trying to make a souffle.
你不相信
Who is trying?
我会让你知道
I will have you know
我在大学赢得了KPT兄弟会烘培大赛冠军
that I won the Kappa-Pi-Tau bake-off in college, okay?
你的兄弟会还有烘培大赛
Your fraternity had a bake-off?
我们为慈善组织筹集了很多善款
Well, we raised a lot of money for charity,
而且严格来说  那是个兄弟姐妹会
and technically, it was a fratority.
男女都有  没有会堂
Co-ed. No house.
天哪  你真的是个书呆子
Oh, God, you are such a nerd.
的确如此  但是有人
Guilty as charged, but somebody else
在我们应该享受浪漫晚餐时
is working on a science experiment
还在操心科学研究项目
when we're supposed to be having a romantic make-up dinner.
所以  那个有那么重要吗
So, what's so important anyway?
好的  你记得你说过你会
Okay, so you know how you said
对我有时做的事情
you were going to be more open-minded
保持开放的态度吧
about the things that I sometimes do?
是的  我是真的那么想
Yeah. And I meant that.
好的  所以我在用生物传递系统改写基因
Okay, so I was using a biolistic delivery system
这样我就可以治愈癌症  脊髓硬化症
in order to rewrite DNA, so I could cure cancer, ALS...
基本上所有的疾病
Basically, all disease.
突然  我有了一个重大突破
When, out of nowhere, I had a penicillin moment.
那是个幸运的突破
It's a lucky break.
一开始我以为让心脏变得坚不可摧
At first, I thought it was just a side effect,
只不过是个副作用
that we had made the heart invulnerable,
但紧接着我意识到我可以用生物传递系统
but then I realized that I could use the delivery system
提升人类力量
in order to enhance human powers.
你说的"提升"是什么意思
What do you mean by "Enhance"?
你记得
Do you remember the
我们在感恩节的假设讨论吗
hypothetical discussion we had at Thanksgiving?
是的  关于给予人类超能力
Yeah, about giving humans superpowers?
力量  速度  无坚不摧的能力
Strength, speed, invulnerability...
-但那是不可能的  -是  我也这么认为
- But that's impossible. - Yeah, I thought so, too.
直到我亲眼看见实验结果
Until I saw it with my own eyes.
等等  你想告诉我你成功做到了这个
Wait. Hold on. Are you telling me that you've achieved this?
我很接近了
I'm close.
好的  我知道关于
Okay, and I know there are
它的用法会有质疑
going to be questions about its applications,
所以我才特别想告诉你
which is why I was dying to tell you,
因为我需要你  詹姆斯  好吗
because I need you, James, okay?
我需要你当我"肩上的天使"
I need you as the angel on my shoulder,
这样我才能确定正确路线
so that I can determine the right course.
你支持我吗
Do I have your support?
支持
Yes.
这栋楼被完全封锁了
The building is hermetically sealed.
周界警报激活了
Perimeter alarms are active.
如果莫拉人进来  我们会收到消息
If the Morae enter, we will hear about it.
他们进来的话怎么办
So, what happens when they do get in?
我们怎么看见隐形人呢
How do we see the invisible?
莫拉人天生的隐形能力
Well, the Morae's natural
和光不会相互作用
cloaking ability does not interact with light,
但我们会让雾弥漫通道
however, we will flood the corridor with mist
通过激发辐射
and activate a grid of light amplification
激活光放大系统
by stimulated emissions of radiation.
激光束
Laser beams?
很好  你很熟悉这项技术
Good, you're familiar with the technology.
一旦莫拉人破坏了激光
Once the Morae disrupt the lasers,
我会用这家伙向他们开火
I will fire at them with this bad boy.
那是彩弹枪吗
Is that a paintball gun?
是的  它会装载这些磷光子弹
Yes, which will be loaded with these phosphorescent pellets.
一旦他们染上记号...
Once they are marked...
莫拉人就会成为活靶子  聪明
That makes the Morae easy targets. It's good thinking.
那是自然
Well, obviously.
当然了  如果其他都不行
And, of course, if all else fails,
总是会有S计划
there's always Plan S.
好了  所有人把你们的眩晕枪调到四档
All right, everybody. Set your stun guns to level four.
伤害足够让他们现身了
That's just enough to injure them, so they uncloak.
我们不用眩晕枪  我们用的是真枪
We're not using stun guns. We're using real guns.
使用致命武器
The use of lethal force
违反了超查部的规定
is against DEO policy.
对不起  局长  这是哈雷上校的命令
I'm sorry, Director, but those were Colonel Haley's orders.
今天下午谭将军发生这些事以后
After everything that happened with Tan this afternoon,
我本来准备走
I was ready to walk,
但出于责任  我留下来了
but, out of duty, I stayed.
为了保护她和这个地方
To protect her and this place.
但我不能再和她一起工作了  卡拉
But, look, I can't work with her anymore, Kara.
我在听
I hear you.
听着  我们的价值观完全不同
Look, we have a completely different value system.
我忍不了她的方法
I do not condone her methods.
我愿意献出生命来拯救这个国家
I would give my life to save this country.
你知道的
You know that.
但有像哈雷这样的人管事
But I cannot be part of a DEO
我就没法待在超查部
that has someone like Haley in charge.
她毫无道德
She has no morality.
她没有底线
There's no line in the sand.
我要辞职了  卡拉
I'm gonna resign, Kara.
艾丽克斯  你不能离开超查部
Okay, Alex, you can't leave the DEO.
我在这待不下去了
I can't stay here.
你是部门的道德中心
You are its moral center.
特工们需要你
The agents need you.
国家需要你
The country needs you.
你走了  哈雷就没人盯着了
Without you, Haley would go unchecked.
每次见到她  都得憋着
Every time I see her, I just wanna let loose.
只要你想  你就能扳倒她
You would flatten her if you did.
然后我会上军事法庭  她就赢了
Then I would be court-martialed, and she would win.
我不会让她赢的
I'm not gonna let her win.
艾丽克斯  你是我认识的
Alex, you are the most fearless
最勇敢最坚定的人
and determined person I know.
很抱歉我不能与你同舟共济
I'm sorry I can't be there to do this with you.
即使你不在这里  我也知道你总是支持我
Even when you're not here, I know you've always got my back.
S计划  总是如此
Plan S. Always.
总是如此
Always.
哈雷上校
Colonel Haley.
对不起  丹弗斯局长
I'm so sorry, Director Danvers.
你骗了我  丹弗斯
You had me fooled, Danvers.
我以为你是个诚实的军人
I thought you were a soldier.
但我发现了这个
But then I find this out.
发现了你的谎言
All the lies you must have told.
为了保护你自己的妹妹
You have undermined everything that we stand for,
你破坏了我们的主张
all to protect your own sister.
超女
Supergirl.
他们来了
They're here.
好了  大家听好了
All right, everyone. Listen up.
所有人上膛准备
Everyone, lock and load.
这些生物是狩猎者
These creatures, they're hunters.
他们杀人不眨眼
They will not hesitate to kill any of you.
你们一看到激光中断
The moment you see a disruption in the lasers,
就开火
open fire.
好了  我们走  我们走
All right, let's go. Let's go.
记住楼里有两个莫拉人
Remember there are two Morae in the building.
大家放松
Easy, everyone.
我们还是能看到他们穿过薄雾
We should still see them coming through the mist.
如果我们互相支持
If we have each other's backs,
我们就能克服这一关
we're going to get through this.
尽量活捉
Take them alive if you can.
开火
Fire!
停火
Hold fire.
我们搞定了吗
Did we get it?
解除戒备  丹佛斯
Stand down, Danvers.
赖夫
Reiff.
我找到他了
I got him.
在这里
Over here.
干掉一个
One down.
坏了
Oh, sprock.
多克斯特工
Agent Dox.
不
No.
在那里
It's there!
大家保持密集队形  帮我把多克斯拉回来
Everybody, close ranks. Help me get Dox back.
快走  快走
Move. Move.
退后
Fall back!
你们看到了吗
Do you see it?
我找不到了
I can't find it.
在我们上面
It's on us!
不  去看看特工们  快去
No. Go. Go, check the agents. Go.
你救了我
You saved me.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
从现在开始  你要照我说的做
And from now on, you will do exactly as I order.
完全听我的命令
Exactly when I say.
她刚刚救了你一命
She just saved your life.
我准你说话了吗  丹弗斯
Did I give you permission to speak, Danvers?
你该庆幸你没有因为违反
You're lucky you're not in handcuffs for violating Article 90
军事审判统一法典第90条而被拷起来
of the Uniform Code of Military Justice.
你的指挥权归我了
Your command is now mine.
卡拉·丹弗斯的生活结束了
Kara Danvers' life is over.
一个新闻记者执行秘密军事行动
A member of the press working out of a secret military operation.
我将向总统建议
I'm going to recommend to the President
马上征召你回来执行任务
we immediately conscript you back into service.
如果你对服从命令有任何意见
And if you have any reservations about obeying,
你就想想如果你的敌人
you think about what would happen
知道了你的真实身份会怎样
if your enemies found out who you are.
你的朋友  你的家人
Your friends, your family,
你关心的每个人都会成为目标
everyone you care about would have a target on their back.
我必须要这样
I had to.
-她发现了  -发现什么了
- She found out. - Found out what?
她知道我是超女了
She knows I'm Supergirl.
-你们俩还好吗  -还行
- You two okay? - We're okay.
我干的
I did that.
-她有告诉其他人吗  -没有
- Did she tell anyone? - No.
荣恩  我们叫你过来是因为
J'onn, we called you here because...
你们想让我抹去她的记忆
You want me to wipe her mind.
对  把她知道一切关于超女的都抹掉
Yeah. Erase everything she knows about Supergirl.
入侵人的思想也是一种暴力
Invading someone's mind is a form of violence.
我对曼彻斯特做过  我真的不该那样做
I did it with Manchester, and I really shouldn't have.
-那我们另想办法  -是的
- We'll find another way. - Yeah.
我来吧
I'll do it.
我当然会做
Of course, I'll do it.
我不知道那种油漆多久才会消失
I didn't realize quite how permanent that paint was going to be.
如果这是昨天袭击造成的唯一永远伤害
Well, if this is the only lasting damage from yesterday's attack,
那我可以接受
then I will take it.
是这样的  当我摔在阳台上时
There's that, and I badly bruised my tailbone
重伤了我的尾椎骨
when I fell over the balcony.
所以你要这样走路吗
Is that why you're walking like that?
-别笑了  -有淤青吗
- Don't laugh. - It's a bruise?
-我这是七级疼痛  -抱歉
- My pain is at a seven. - Sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我不知道地球上也有这个
I didn't know they had those on Earth.
它没在资料库里
It wasn't in the database.
那是什么
What is that?
那是个维特拉人
That creature is a Vertullarian.
是求真者
A Truth Seeker.
既然我们已经结束了昨天的混乱
Well, now that we're done with the excitement from yesterday,
我们可以继续调查
we can carry on with the investigation
超女的身份了
into Supergirl's identity.
今天之内  我要搞定她
By the end of the day, I'll get her.
没人能欺骗一个求真者
There's no way to deceive a Truth Seeker.
它有一个能力  揭露谎言
It has one function, to expose lies.
所有知道超女秘密身份的人
Anyone who knows Supergirl's secret identity
都处于极大危险之中
is at incredible risk.
荣恩不能抹去哈雷
J'onn can't erase Haley's intention
想找到她身份的想法
of finding her identity.
我们能控制的是她得到信息的途径
What we can control is her access to the information.
那我们要抹去超查部里所有
So, we wipe the minds of everyone at the DEO
知道我是超女的人的记忆
who knows I'm Supergirl.
就像哈雷一样
Just like with Haley,
我得抹去他们所有能把
I'll go in and erase every memory they have
卡拉和超女联系起来的记忆
that connects Kara with Supergirl.
那样做你没意见吗
Are you okay doing that?
他们都同意了  他们想保护你
They've given their consent. They want to protect you.
好吧
Okay.
我也必须清除记忆
I have to be mind-wiped, too.
什么
What?
不  我必须这样
No, I have to.
不行  这不可能
No, it's out of the question.
听着  即使我能骗过求真者
Look, even if I could beat the Truth Seeker,
我还是会有犯错的危险
there'd still be a danger that I would slip up,
发发短信  或是共享信息
you know, with a text or just sharing information
又或者仅仅因为你是我妹妹
or simply the fact that you are my sister
而且我爱你
and I love you.
那你就必须更精明  更谨慎
So, you'll be smarter and more careful.
如果艾丽克斯的记忆没有被抹去
If Alex's mind isn't wiped,
哈雷百分之百
there is a 100% certainty
会发现你的秘密身份
that Haley will still discover your secret identity.
我刚从一个
I just came back from a world
你不认识我的世界回来
where you didn't know who I was.
我不想再经历一次了
I'm not doing that again.
-没其他办法了  -有
- There's no other way. - There is.
你可以辞职  直接走  离开那里
You can quit. Just leave. Get out of there.
-卡拉  -如果你不在那里工作
- Kara... - Haley's not a danger to you
-哈雷对你就没有威胁  -我不能辞职
- when you don't work there. - I can't quit.
你之前也说过
You said it before.
我必须留下  我必须从内部与其斗争
I have to stay, and I have to fight this from within.
没有了你  我就不是我了
Who am I without you?
我成为超女的真正目的
The whole reason I became Supergirl was...
就是为了救你
It was to save you.
我还会是这个目的
And I'm still gonna be the reason.
我还是我
I'm still gonna be me.
你也还是卡拉  我的妹妹
And you're still gonna be Kara, my sister.
我只是
I just...
我不会知道你是超女了
I won't know that you're Supergirl.
那我每天都要骗你
I'll have to lie to you every day.
那不是谎言  那是
It's not a lie. It's...
那是保守一个秘密
It's keeping a secret.
而且我允许你有秘密
And I'm giving you permission.
这一次让我来救你
Now let me save you this time.
梅芙  怎么了
Hey, Maeve. What's up?
可以啊  我可以聊妈妈的生日
Uh, yeah. Yeah, I can talk about Mom's birthday.
没有  没有什么重要的事
No. Nothing important.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
一切都会好的
Everything's gonna be okay.
我受不了了
I can't.